Guide to the Dick Thornburgh Papers, 1932- AIS.1998.30.18
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Photographs, 1932-2004; XVIII.
  - Governor of Pennsylvania, 1979-1987; 9.
    - Events and People
      - Conversations with the Governor with Senator Jim Kelly and Senator Stuart Greenleaf, December 5, 1984 (Box 1508, Folder 4)
      - Cosby, Bill at Governor's Arts Awards (3), May 8, 1984 (Box 1508, Folder 5)
      - Crane, Stanley, Conrail Pier 124, Philadelphia, PA, February 11, 1983 (Box 1508, Folder 6)
      - Crestview Elementary School, Carlisle, PA, April 17, 1984 (Box 1508, Folder 7)
      - Cronkite, Walter in Philadelphia, PA (2), June 17, 1982 (Box 1508, Folder 8)
      - Crosstown Bridge Groundbreaking, Pittsburgh, PA (1), March 8, 1984 (Box 1508, Folder 9)
      - Curl, Louise, Tori, and Forrest, Peter Adams, and Mildred and Jim Sporny (1), undated (Box 1508, Folder 10)
      - People's Republic of China Trip (383), March, 1980 (Box 1508, Folder 11 to 17)
      - Hong Kong, March, 1980 (Box 1508, Folder 18)
      - China/Japan Reunion Dinner at the Governor's Home (9), May 9, 1980 (Box 1508, Folder 19)
      - People's Republic of China (12), December, 1983 (Box 1509, Folder 1)
      - People's Republic of China, Provincial Governors at the Governor's Home (1), May 2, 1985 (Box 1509, Folder 2)
      - People's Republic of China, Ambassador Han Xu (13), August 13, 1986 (Box 1509, Folder 3)
      - Dallastown Area High School, Anthracite Demonstration Dedication Ceremony, Dallastown, PA (1), March 12, 1986 (Box 1509, Folder 4)
      - Davis, Secretary William, Testimonial Dinner, Greensburg, PA (2), 1979 (Box 1509, Folder 5)
      - de Margerie, His Excellency Emmanuel, French Ambassador (1), undated (Box 1509, Folder 6)
      - Dennis, DCA Secretary Shirley, undated (Box 1509, Folder 7)
      - Denton, Dr. Harold (4), March 27, 1980 (Box 1509, Folder 8)
      - Denver, Colorado GOP Leaders, August, 1980 (Box 1509, Folder 9)
      - Department of General Services, Harrisburg (4), June 13, 1979 (Box 1509, Folder 10)
      - Dole, Secretary Elizabeth, Philadelphia, PA (2), April 25, 1984 (Box 1509, Folder 11)
      - Dressler Center, Somerset County (2), 1986 (Box 1509, Folder 12)
      - D'Souza, P.P., Consul General of India in New York, Courtesy Call, Harrisburg (1), April 29, 1982 (Box 1509, Folder 13)
      - Dukakis, Governor Michael, CONEG, Danbury, CT (1), 1984 (Box 1509, Folder 14)
      - Dunn, Commissioner Daniel (7), undated (Box 1509, Folder 15)
      - DuPont, Governor Pierre (1), March 10, 1986 (Box 1509, Folder 16)
      - Eckley Mine Village Visit, Eckley, PA (2), August 27, 1980 (Box 1509, Folder 17)
      - Eddy Creek Coal Breaker Painting in Governor Dick Thornburgh's Office, Harrisburg, PA (4), May 4, 1979 (Box 1509, Folder 18)
      - Egypt Album (47), November, 1980 (Box 1509, Folder 19)
      - Eisenhower, Mrs. Dwight (Mamie) at Historic Gettysburg Ceremony(10), November 14, 1978 (Box 1509, Folder 20)
      - Ellwood City Industrial Park Tour, Ellwood City, PA (1), September 17, 1980 (Box 1509, Folder 21)
      - Engler, Senator John, Lansing MI (1), Probably April, 1983 (Box 1509, Folder 22)
      - Enterprise Avenue Superfund Southwest Philadelphia Water Pollution Treatment Plant with Mayor Wilson Goode (1), May 14, 1984 (Box 1509, Folder 23)
      - Eye Institute at the Pennsylvania College of Optometry, Philadelphia, PA (2), October, 1982 (Box 1509, Folder 24)
      - Fallingwater Pavilion Dedication with Edgar Kaufmann and Josh Whetzel (3), June 3, 1981 (Box 1510, Folder 1)
      - Farmers (6), 1979-1986 (Box 1510, Folder 2)
      - Fish, Henry (1), June 26, 1981 (Box 1510, Folder 3)
      - Fitzgerald, Jim (2), September 30, 1979 (Box 1510, Folder 4)
      - Flaherty, Pete at former Mayor Joseph Barr's funeral (1), August 30, 1982 (Box 1510, Folder 5)
      - Ford, President Gerald (6), undated (Box 1510, Folder 6)
      - Ford, Harrison on the set for Witness, Lancaster, PA (37), June 20, 1984 (Box 1510, Folder 7)
      - Franklin, Ben (1), undated (Box 1510, Folder 8)
      - Gasohol Inauguration, Harrisburg, PA (1), November 5, 1979 (Box 1510, Folder 9)
      - Gaydos, Congressman Joseph (2), September, 1981 (Box 1510, Folder 10)
      - Geist, Representative Rick and Miss Pennsylvania for 1982-1983, Harrisburg, PA (1), undated (Box 1510, Folder 11)
      - George Washington Carver High School Commencement (3), June 20, 1985 (Box 1510, Folder 12)
      - Getty, James as Abraham Lincoln (5), undated (Box 1510, Folder 13)
      - Rededication of the Gettysburg Memorial, March 18, 1985 (Box 1510, Folder 14)
      - Giametti, President A. Bartlett of Yale University (1), undated (Box 1510, Folder 15)
      - Gillis, Provost B.T. of Youngstown State University (1), undated (Box 1510, Folder 16)
      - Gleason, Commonwealth Secretary and Family at Swearing-In Ceremony (1), January 29, 1986 (Box 1510, Folder 17)
      - Goldman, Elliot (1), April, 1982 (Box 1510, Folder 18)
      - Goldstein, Bob, Associate Deputy Secretary of PennDOT (1), undated (Box 1510, Folder 19)
      - Governor's Coal Conference (5), January 23, 1980 (Box 1510, Folder 20)
      - "Governor Dick" Mountain, Lebanon County, PA (2), October 21, 1979 (Box 1510, Folder 21)
      - Governor's Office, Harrisburg, PA (20), 1979-1986 (Box 1510, Folder 22)
      - Governor's School for the Arts at Bucknell University, Lewisburg, PA (4), 1984 (Box 1510, Folder 23)
      - Grand Ole Opry, Nashville, TN (2), April 4, 1981 (Box 1510, Folder 24)
      - Grand Ole Opry, National Governors' Association Summer Meeting, Nashville, TN (1), July, 1984 (Box 1510, Folder 25)
      - Greater Johnstown Chamber of Commerce, Annual Dinner Meeting, July 12, 1979 (Box 1510, Folder 26)
      - Green, Mayor William (Bill), Harrisburg, PA (2), April 26, 1983 (Box 1510, Folder 27)
      - Greensboro Bicentennial Banquet, Greensboro, PA (1), July 18, 1981 (Box 1510, Folder 28)
      - Greenwood, Representative James (1), 1983 (Box 1510, Folder 29)
      - Grimaldi, Prince Albert (1), July 13, 1985 (Box 1510, Folder 30)
      - Gross, Kathy, Iranian Hostage (7), December 4, 1979 (Box 1510, Folder 31)
      - Gruppo, Representative Leonard (1), July, 1986 (Box 1510, Folder 32)
      - Haabestad, Harold (Bud) (2), July 27, 1981 (Box 1510, Folder 33)
      - Hager, Henry and Robert Jubelirer (1), undated (Box 1510, Folder 34)
      - Hands Across America, Philadelphia, PA (2), May 25, 1986 (Box 1510, Folder 35)
      - Hardhats (8), 1979-1986 (Box 1510, Folder 36)
      - Harlem Globetrotters (2), March 11, 1986 (Box 1510, Folder 37)
      - Harris, Franco (Pittsburgh Steeler) (4), undated (Box 1510, Folder 38)
      - Harrisburg Senators (2), April 11, 1987 (Box 1511, Folder 1)
      - Hay, Wally (1), undated (Box 1511, Folder 2)
      - Hayman, Wayne at Children's Hospital, Philadelphia, PA (1), December 15, 1982 (Box 1511, Folder 3)
      - Hazelton Area Students (2), November 18, 1985 (Box 1511, Folder 4)
      - Hazlett Memorial Awards (5), 1980, 1984-1986 (Box 1511, Folder 5)
      - Heifetz, Daniel and Janne (2), November 19, 1981 (Box 1511, Folder 6)
      - Heinz, Senator John at Knoll International (1), October 14, 1982 (Box 1511, Folder 7)
      - Heinz, John and Richard Schweiker, undated (Box 1511, Folder 8)
      - Meeting with Hispanic Leaders, September, 1983 (Box 1511, Folder 9)
      - Holl, Senator Edwin, Civil Air Patrol (1), undated (Box 1511, Folder 10)
      - Homestead Economic Revitalization Corp., Homestead, PA (1), April 19, 1979 (Box 1511, Folder 11)
      - Howse, Jennifer, Deputy Secretary, Office of Mental Retardation, Public Welfare (1), undated (Box 1511, Folder 12)
      - Hunt, Governor James (1), undated (Box 1511, Folder 13)
      - I-95 Opening with Mayor Wilson Goode and Secretary Tom Larson ((4), December 16, 1985 (Box 1511, Folder 14)
      - Indiana County Visit, Indiana County, PA (6), August 16, 1979 (Box 1511, Folder 15)
      - Indiana University of Pennsylvania Spring Commencement (10), May 14, 1983 (Box 1511, Folder 16)
      - International Hunter Education Week Proclamation Ceremony/Public Ceremony (1), September 1, 1981 (Box 1511, Folder 17)
      - Intersection of Rodi, Universal and Jefferson Road Opening (1), September 9, 1986 (Box 1511, Folder 18)
      - Israel (35), November, 1980 (Box 1511, Folder 19 to 22)
      - Italian-Americans for Reagan and Bush (1), 1982 (Box 1511, Folder 23)
      - Janis, Byron and Maria Cooper Janis at Governor's Arts Award Ceremony (1), May 13, 1985 (Box 1511, Folder 24)
      - Japan, Tokyo (24), March, 1980 (Box 1511, Folder 25)
      - Jewish National Fund (3), June, 1981 (Box 1511, Folder 26)
      - Job Corps, Pittsburgh, PA (5), October 4, 1984 (Box 1511, Folder 27)
      - Johnstown Transportation Center Dedication Ceremony, Johnstown, PA (5), July 17, 1981 (Box 1511, Folder 28)
      - Jones, Secretary Clifford (2), March, 1979 (Box 1511, Folder 29)
      - Jubelirer, Senator Robert (1), undated (Box 1511, Folder 30)
      - Kandes, Frank (1), 1984 (Box 1512, Folder 1)
      - Kanuck, Representative George (1), February 20, 1979 (Box 1512, Folder 2)
      - Karekin II, Catholicos of the Great House of Cilicia, Courtesy Call, Harrisburg (4), June 27, 1983 (Box 1512, Folder 3)
      - Keeler, Bishop William H., Harrisburg, PA (2), January 4, 1984 (Box 1512, Folder 4)
      - "Keep Pennsylvania Beautiful" Day (4), April 25, 1981 (Box 1512, Folder 5)
      - John B. Kelly Luncheon (John B. Kelly III and Sandra Kelly) (2), June 14, 1985 (Box 1512, Folder 6)
      - Keystone State Games, Opening Ceremony, Penn State University (1), August 13, 1983 (Box 1512, Folder 7)
      - Kim, Dr. Kyung-Won, Ambassador for South Korea to United Nations (Henry Fish, AMSCO), Erie, PA (3), June 7, 1983 (Box 1512, Folder 8)
      - King, Coretta Scott (3), undated (Box 1512, Folder 9)
      - King, Martin Luther Jr. Day (2), undated (Box 1512, Folder 10)
      - King, Don (1), undated (Box 1512, Folder 11)
      - Kirkpatrick-Lockhart "Welcome Home, Dick" Sign (1), 1987 (Box 1512, Folder 12)
      - Kissinger, Dr. Henry (4), undated (Box 1512, Folder 13)
      - Knoll International Ribbon Cutting and Groundbreaking, East Greenville, PA (3), October 14, 1982 (Box 1512, Folder 14)
      - Kramer, Mrs. Ilva, Pennsylvania Mother of the Year (1), April 14, 1981 (Box 1512, Folder 15)
      - Kraus, Sgt. Kenneth L., Presented the Pennsylvania Cross of Valor (3), March 5, 1979 (Box 1512, Folder 16)
      - Krol, John, Cardinal, Philadelphia, PA, September 22, 1982 (Box 1512, Folder 17)
      - Krol, John, Cardinal, Harrisburg, PA, undated (Box 1512, Folder 18)
      - Liquor Control Board Announcement (3), undated (Box 1512, Folder 19)
      - Lafayette College Commencement, Easton, PA (3), May 30, 1982 (Box 1512, Folder 20)
      - Lamb, Brian P., President of C-SPAN, Harrisburg, PA (1), October 25, 1984 (Box 1512, Folder 21)
      - Larson, Secretary Thomas L. (1), undated (Box 1512, Folder 22)
      - Leese, Douglas S., London, England (4), January, 1984 (Box 1512, Folder 23)
      - Lehigh Electric Project, Old Forge, PA (3), September 17, 1981 (Box 1512, Folder 24)
      - Lehigh University NSF Engineering Research Center (3), undated (Box 1512, Folder 25)
      - Legislative Dinner "Travel Person of the Year" (6), 1980 (Box 1512, Folder 26)
      - Levi, Edward, Former U.S. Attorney General, Department of Justice, Washington, DC (1), undated (Box 1512, Folder 27)
      - Likins, Peter, President of Lehigh University (1), November 12, 1986 (Box 1512, Folder 28)
      - Lincoln University Commencement (1), May 6, 1979 (Box 1512, Folder 29)
      - Little League World Series, Williamsport, PA (3), August 25, 1979 (Box 1512, Folder 30)
      - Main Street Dedication, Bethlehem, PA (26), June 9, 1979 (Box 1512, Folder 31)
      - Mascots (1), undated (Box 1512, Folder 32)
      - "Math Counts" National Championship Competitors, Harrisburg (4), April 26, 1986 (Box 1512, Folder 33)
      - McAuliffe-Resnick Scholarship Announcement at Carnegie Mellon University, Pittsburgh, PA (1), 1986 (Box 1512, Folder 34)
      - McDermott, Judge James (1), October 5, 1981 (Box 1512, Folder 35)
      - McFarland, Joseph of Geneva College, Harrisburg (2), March 28, 1985 (Box 1512, Folder 36)
      - Meany, George, National President of AFL-CIO, Memorial Mass, Philadelphia, PA (1), January 21, 1980 (Box 1512, Folder 37)
      - Meese, Attorney General Edwin at Spring Garden College Commencement, Philadelphia, PA (1), October 6, 1985 (Box 1512, Folder 38)
      - "Meet the Press" (2), 1980 (Box 1512, Folder 39)
      - Mercersburg Academy (1), undated (Box 1512, Folder 40)
      - Meyer, General Edward C. at Presentation of the Pennsylvania Distinguished Service Medal (2), August 26, 1982 (Box 1512, Folder 41)
      - Michener, James at Governor's Arts Award Ceremony (1), May 5, 1981 (Box 1512, Folder 42)
      - Miele, Jerry, Welcome Home Celebration, Mt. Pleasant, PA (2), February 5, 1981 (Box 1512, Folder 43)
      - Minimum Mandatory Sentencing Ad, undated (Box 1512, Folder 44)
      - Mining and Mechanical Institute (1), undated (Box 1513, Folder 1)
      - Miss Pennsylvania, Caroline Black (1), July, 1979 (Box 1513, Folder 2)
      - Miss Teen World and Miss Pennsylvania Teen World, undated (Box 1513, Folder 3)
      - Mobile Museum, 300th Birthday Ribbon Cutting and Proclamation Ceremony (4), March 4, 1982 (Box 1513, Folder 4)
      - Mock, Joshua, 1986 Capitol Tree Lighting Ceremony (1) (Box 1513, Folder 5)
      - Modeidin, Dr. Fouad, Acting Prime Minister, Egypt (1), November, 1980 (Box 1513, Folder 6)
      - Mothers Against Drunk Driving (MADD), undated (Box 1513, Folder 7)
      - Mugabe, Prime Minister Robert of Zimbabwe, Pittsburgh, PA (1), October 3, 1984 (Box 1513, Folder 8)
      - Nader, Sam, Oneonta, NY (1), August 12, 1984 (Box 1513, Folder 9)
      - National Association of Former United States Attorneys, San Diego, CA (1), April 11, 1983 (Box 1513, Folder 10)
      - National Governor's Association (3), undated (Box 1513, Folder 11)
      - NEC Corporation, Harrisburg (2), February 1, 1984 (Box 1513, Folder 12)
      - Nelson, Lynn, Executive Director of the Bureau of State Lotteries (1), June 30, 1984 (Box 1513, Folder 13)
      - Nixon, Richard M. (1), February 5, 1987 (Box 1513, Folder 14)
      - Nguyen, Minhson at Computer with Governor (1), undated (Box 1513, Folder 15)
      - O'Hara Quote (1), undated (Box 1513, Folder 16)
      - O'Kawara, Ambassador of Japan (1), May 28, 1982 (Box 1513, Folder 17)
      - Operation DIG (22), June 13, 1981 (Box 1513, Folder 18)
      - Outside Capitol (1), undated (Box 1513, Folder 19)
      - PAT Labor Bill Signing Ceremony (3), undated (Box 1513, Folder 20)
      - Pittsburgh Plate Glass Building Topping-Off Ceremony Mayor Richard Caliguiri), Pittsburgh, PA (3), July 29, 1982 (Box 1513, Folder 21)
      - P.P.T.N. Town Meeting with John Dimsdale, WITF-TV, Hershey, PA (1), June 30, 1980 (Box 1513, Folder 22)
      - Palmer, Arnold (5), 1979-1986 (Box 1513, Folder 23)
      - Palmer, Arnold, Press Conference, Harrisburg (1), September 30, 1980 (Box 1513, Folder 24)
      - Papoulias, George, Greek Ambassador to the U.S., Courtesy Call, Harrisburg (2), April 26, 1985 (Box 1513, Folder 25)
      - Parades (2), 1979-1986 (Box 1513, Folder 26)
      - Parkway Opening (6), November, 1981 (Box 1513, Folder 27)
      - Paterno, Joe (1), 1985 (Box 1513, Folder 28)
      - Pearl, Minnie, Grinders Switch, TN (10), July, 1984 (Box 1513, Folder 29)
      - Penn State Nittany Lions (1), January, 1987 (Box 1513, Folder 30)
      - Penn State University Biotechnology Institute Dedication (1), August 9, 1985 (Box 1513, Folder 31)
      - Pennsylvania Academy of Fine Arts (1), May 8, 1985 (Box 1513, Folder 32)
      - Pennsylvania Ballet (1), undated (Box 1513, Folder 33)
      - Pennsylvania Bicycling Guide Photographs, Harrisburg (2), July 24, 1985 (Box 1513, Folder 34)
      - Pennsylvania Catholic Conference, Harrisburg, PA (2), July 9, 1982 (Box 1513, Folder 35)
      - Pennsylvania Chiefs of Police, 70th Annual Conference, Monroeville, PA (6), July 13, 1983 (Box 1513, Folder 36)
      - Pennsylvania Citizens for Better Libraries (1), October 15, 1981 (Box 1513, Folder 37)
      - Pennsylvania Day, Washington, DC (1), September 15, 1981 (Box 1513, Folder 38)
      - Pennsylvania Derby Keystone Racetrack, Bensalem, PA (8), May 30, 1983 (Box 1513, Folder 39)
      - Pennsylvania Electoral College (3), December 17, 1984 (Box 1513, Folder 40)
      - Pennsylvania Federation of Sportsmen's Clubs, Harrisburg (4), July 21, 1981 (Box 1513, Folder 41)
      - Pennsylvania Federation of Sportsmen's Clubs, Inc., Carlisle, PA (4), July 22, 1982 (Box 1513, Folder 42)
      - Pennsylvania Legislative Day, Owens-Illinois (1), June 1, 1981 (Box 1513, Folder 43)
      - Pennsylvania National Guard, undated (Box 1513, Folder 44)
      - Pennsylvania School for the Deaf with Rep. Frank Salvatore, undated (Box 1513, Folder 45)
      - Pennsylvania Society Dinner (2), December, 1986 (Box 1513, Folder 46)
      - Pennsylvania State College Conference, Football Coaches Association, Harrisburg (4), May 12, 1982 (Box 1513, Folder 47)
      - Pennsylvania State Fire Academy, Lewistown, PA (2), June 22, 1984 (Box 1513, Folder 48)
      - Pennsylvania State Mayors Convention (3), July 21-25, 1979 (Box 1513, Folder 49)
      - Pennsylvania State Police Cadet Graduation (2), January 13, 1987 (Box 1513, Folder 50)
      - Pennsylvania Turnpike Commissioners Press Conference (6), May, 1985 (Box 1513, Folder 51)
      - Pennsylvanian Amtrak Passenger Train, April 26, 1980 (Box 1514, Folder 1)
      - Philadelphia council of neighborhood Organizations (1), July 19, 1979 (Box 1514, Folder 2)
      - Philadelphia Mummers (3), 1979-1986 (Box 1514, Folder 3)
      - Philadelphia Port Corporation Check Presentation with Mayor Wilson Goode and Secretary Shirley Dennis (3), March 20, 1985 (Box 1514, Folder 4)
      - Pier 124 (7), December 17, 1980 (Box 1514, Folder 5)
      - Pirates Opener (4), 1985 (Box 1514, Folder 6)
      - Pittsburgh Subway "T" Opening Ceremony (10), July 3, 1985 (Box 1514, Folder 7)
      - Pittston 4.7 Million Dollar Contract for Mine Subsidence Control Project with Mayor Robert Loftus (2), May 18, 1983 (Box 1514, Folder 8)
      - Pocono Mountain Middle School Math Class (3), October 20, 1983 (Box 1514, Folder 9)
      - Poland, Consul General, New York, NY (1), September, 1981 (Box 1514, Folder 10)
      - Police (4), 1979-1986 (Box 1514, Folder 11)
      - Office of Policy Development Staff and other Office Staff(7), undated (Box 1514, Folder 12)
      - Pope John Paul II, Philadelphia, PA (42), October 3, 1979 (Box 1514, Folder 13-16)
      - His Holiness, Pope John Paul II, Philadelphia, PA: Album 1 (62), October 3, 1979 (Box 1514, Folder 17)
      - His Holiness, Pope John Paul II, Philadelphia, PA: Album 2 (62), October 3, 1979 (Box 1515, Folder 1)
      - Prescription Drug Announcement, south Philadelphia community Center (3), November 19, 1984 (Box 1515, Folder 2)
      - Press Conferences (2), 1979-1986 (Box 1515, Folder 3)
      - Project Pelion (1), September 22, 1981 (Box 1515, Folder 4)
      - Previn, Andre, Pittsburgh Symphony, Harrisburg, PA (1), March 9, 1981 (Box 1515, Folder 5)
      - Princess Grace Foundation (2), February 17-18, 1984 (Box 1515, Folder 6)
      - Pulaski Day (1), October 3, 1982 (Box 1515, Folder 7)
      - Quaker Oats (8), September 7, 1983 (Box 1515, Folder 8)
      - Randolph, Senator Jennings, West Virginia (4), 1983 (Box 1515, Folder 9)
      - Raia, Vic and Santa (1), undated (Box 1515, Folder 10)
      - Reading State Office Building Ribbon Cutting Ceremony (2), August 13, 1982 (Box 1515, Folder 11)
      - Reagan, Maureen (4), undated (Box 1515, Folder 12)
      - Reagan, Nancy (4), 1982-1984 (Box 1515, Folder 13)
      - Reagan, President Ronald, Visit to Sun Ship (3), August, 1980 (Box 1516, Folder 1)
      - Reagan, President Ronald, Formal Events (9), 1981-1987 (Box 1516, Folder 2)
      - Reagan, President Ronald, Meetings (10), 1981-1986 (Box 1516, Folder 3)
      - Reagan, President Ronald, Campaigning at Bellevue-Stratford Hotel, Philadelphia, PA (9), 1982 (Box 1516, Folder 4)
      - Reagan, President Ronald at Control Data Institute, Pittsburgh, PA (6), April 6, 1983 (Box 1516, Folder 5)
      - National Conference on Dislocated Workers, Pittsburgh, PA (6), April 6, 1983 (Box 1516, Folder 6)
      - Reagan, President Ronald at Republican Governor's Association (5), Fall, 1983 (Box 1516, Folder 7)
      - Reagan, President Ronald at Shrine of Our Lady of Czestochowa, Doylestown, PA (8), September 9, 1984 (Box 1516, Folder 8)
      - Reagan, President Ronald (11), 1979-1986 (Box 1516, Folder 9)
      - Reed, Mayor Stephen, Harrisburg, PA (1), September 15, 1982 (Box 1516, Folder 10)
      - Reibman, Senator Jeanette and Atlantic Apparel Contractors Association (1), undated (Box 1516, Folder 11)
      - Renaissance III (3), September, 1985 (Box 1516, Folder 12)
      - Republican Governor's Association, Austin, TX (2), November, 1979 (Box 1516, Folder 13)
      - Republican Governor's Association, St. Louis, MO (4), April 6, 1985 (Box 1516, Folder 14)
      - Republican Governor's Conference, Williamsburg, VA (Album), Winter, 1978 (Box 1516, Folder 15)
      - Republican Governor's Conference, Austen, TX (Album), 1979 (Box 1516, Folder 16)
      - Republican Governor's Conference, Philadelphia, PA (2 Albums), 1980 (Box 1516, Folder 17)
      - Republican Governor's Conference, New Orleans, LA (Album), 1981 (Box 1516, Folder 18)
      - Republican Governor's Association, Kansas City, MO (Album), 1982 (Box 1516, Folder 19)
      - Republican National Convention, Detroit, MI (14), July 14-17, 1980 (Box 1517, Folder 1)
      - Republican State Committee with Peter Thornburgh and Teenage Republicans (1), August 18, 1979 (Box 1517, Folder 2)
      - Republican State Committee Spring Dinner Featuring V.P. George Bush, Philadelphia, PA (6), March, 20, 1985 (Box 1517, Folder 3)
      - Rhodes, Governor James, Columbus, OH (1), December 2, 1981 (Box 1517, Folder 4)
      - Rhodes Scholars (3), January 2, 1985 (Box 1517, Folder 5)
      - Ridgeway, General Matthew (5), June 6, 1980 (Box 1517, Folder 6)
      - Ritter, Congressman Don (1), July, 1980 (Box 1517, Folder 7)
      - Robb, Governor Charles (Chuck) and Governor Harry Hughes (2), undated (Box 1517, Folder 8)
      - Rogers, Mr. Fred (4), undated (Box 1517, Folder 9)
      - Rotary Club (7), undated (Box 1517, Folder 10)
      - ROTC Awards Presentation Ceremony, Harrisburg (3), November 1, 1984 (Box 1517, Folder 11)
      - Russell, Leo (1), undated (Box 1517, Folder 12)
      - Sadat, Madam (2), September 28, 1980 (Box 1517, Folder 13)
      - "Saturn" Presentation (2), February, 1985 (Box 1517, Folder 14)
      - Schuylkill County Event (7), April 24, 1984 (Box 1517, Folder 15)
      - Schweiker, Senator and Mrs. Richard (1), undated (Box 1517, Folder 16)
      - Scranton, Governor W.W.S., Jr. (3), undated (Box 1517, Folder 17)
      - Scranton, Lt. Governor W.W.S., III (3), undated (Box 1517, Folder 18)
      - Scranton, Lt. Governor William, Gubernatorial Announcement (3), February 3, 1986 (Box 1517, Folder 19)
      - Scott, Adjutant General Richard (1), undated (Box 1517, Folder 20)
      - Senior Citizens Center, Harrisburg, PA (3), undated (Box 1517, Folder 21)
      - SEPTA Strike Settlement (1), 1981 (Box 1517, Folder 22)
      - Shafer, Governor Raymond (3), January 30, 1979 (Box 1517, Folder 23)
      - Shrine Circus, Harrisburg, PA (5), 1979 (Box 1517, Folder 24)
      - Shumaker, John for Senate (2), 1983-1984 (Box 1517, Folder 25)
      - Smokey the Bear (1), April 12, 1979 (Box 1517, Folder 26)